前情提要
我想策反火车头
I want to flip A-Train.
我为什么要和你谈
Why the fuck would I ever talk to you?
因为你给了星光那段录像
'Cause you gave Starlight that footage.
监控录像资料被人 从犯罪分析部取走送给星光
Surveillance footage was taken from Crime Analytics and given to Starlight.
她只是需要帮忙
She just wanted some help--
她承认了 泄露消息的人被解决了
She confessed. Leak plugged.
你不认为她要说的下一个词 可能会有用吗
You don't think the next word out of her mouth might've been useful?
我爸快要死了 我需要一剂五号化合物 今天就需要
My dad's about to die. I need a dose of Compound V and I need it today.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
他发现你谋杀了他家人时会怎样
What happens when he finds out you murdered his family?
- 那个人是我 - 什么是你
- It was me. - What was you?
对不起
I'm so sorry.
我恨你
I hate you.
喜美子
Kimiko!
星光去了一家诊所 跑去做了流产
Starlight visited a clinic and she had an abortion.
婴儿杀手
Baby killer!
在拖车里时 我是怎么了
What happened to me back there?
欢迎来到戈多尔金大学
Welcome to Godolkin University.
这个病毒只感染超人类
The virus only affects Supes.
它会跟他们血液里的五号化合物结合
It attaches to the Compound V in their blood.
加强剂量 看看能让她的状况恶化到什么程度
Concentrate the dose. Let's see how sick we can make her.
- 全都在里面了  - 对
Is this all of it? - Yeah.
你是唯一知道如何复制病毒的人
You're the only one who knows how to replicate it.
在充满混乱的世界里 有些东西永远不会改变
In a world of chaos, some things never change.
比如善良无敌 总会获胜
That good will always win.
比如真爱无敌 征服一切
That love conquers all.
比如英雄们总会响应使命的召唤 护国佑民 鼓舞民心
And that heroes will answer the call to protect, to inspire.
美国沃特 1950年
《诅咒傅满洲的瞄准器》1953年
百威 哪里有自由 哪里就有百威 1957年
深红夫人 1967年
阿帕奇大酋长说:“不要乱扔垃圾 克莫萨比” 1970年
V52博览会 受粉丝支持 为粉丝服务
欢迎莅临V52博览会
Welcome to the V52 Expo.
现在 请大家 以热烈的掌声欢迎主持人
Now please give a big round of applause for your hosts
卡梅隆科尔曼和深海登场
Cameron Coleman and The Deep.
祖国人 回家之旅还愉快吗
Homelander. Nice trip home?
座无虚席 他们爱死你了
This turnout. They love the fuck out of you.
真是台好戏啊
Talk about bread and circus.
沃特电影宇宙即将推出的影片 不止这一部
And it's just one of the many new projects we've got coming to you on the VCU timeline.
早七点到晚七点 精彩不停播
Phases seven through 19.
今天 我们将与大家分享所有的细节
Which we'll be sharing with you all today in exhaustive detail.
你还好吗 有耳鸣之类的症状吗
Are you okay? Is there anything, like,
有刺痛或奇怪的感觉吗
buzzing or tingling or... weird?
没有 我跟你说 我感觉很好
No, I'm telling you. I feel great.
- 你确定我之前中风了吗  - 确定
- Are you absolutely sure I had a stroke? - Yes.
你记得的最后一件事是什么
What's the last thing you remember?
我去食品店买家庭装的披萨卷
Let me see... I was at Smart & Final, I was buying a family pack of pizza rolls.
没有意大利辣香肠口味的 我就只好买了至尊披萨卷
They didn't have pepperoni, so I had to get supreme.
- 不然是三种肉类的  - 爸
- Or was it Triple Meat? - Dad.
不 就是至尊披萨卷 我记得 上面点缀着青椒...
No, it was supreme. I remember it had the little green pepper specks in it.
爸 别说披萨卷的事了
Dad! Forget about the fucking pizza rolls.
- 对不起 - 他好像跟原来一样爱跑题
Well, he sure sounds like himself.
要是真像他们说的那么严重 我就活不到这时候了 对吧
Yeah. I mean, if I was as bad as they say, then I-I-I shouldn't be alive, right?
真是个不折不扣的奇迹
I mean, it's a true blue miracle.
休息一下吧 好吗
Why don't you get some rest?
我跟妈去给你买罐思乐宝无糖可乐
Okay? Mom and I are gonna go find you a Diet Snapple.
好的
Okay!
- 你给他注射了五号  - 是的 我以为你想要这样
- You gave him the V? - Yeah. I thought that's what you wanted.
它从你外套里掉了出来 我不明白
It fell out of your coat. I don't understand.
如果不想用 你为什么要带来
Why did you bring it if you didn't want to use it?
我想用来着 我...确实想用来着
Look, I wanted to. I... I did.
但后来又不想了 好吗 我就是...
But then I didn't. Okay? It's just that I've...
我见过用那玩意儿的糟糕下场 见了很多次
I've seen that shit go wrong so many times.
可有时会有好结果 对吧
Well, it's got to go right sometimes, right?
不然就不会有超人类了
I mean, otherwise there wouldn't be any Supes.
看看他 他没事
Look at him. He's fine.
今晚 《沃特最逗的宠物攻击》...
Tonight, on Vought's Funniest Pet Attacks...
从小到大 你都没有母亲的关爱
You grew up without one parent.
一想到你连父亲也要失去 我就于心不忍
I just couldn't bear the thought of you losing another one.
《鞭炮带你看真相》
星光无法决定要强奸还是杀害婴儿
Guess Starlight can't decide whether to rape a baby or kill it.
我要提出故意伤人罪的指控 那是确凿无疑的
Well, I am pressing charges for assault, and that's for damn sure.
尽管警方说她有不在场证明
And even though the police say she had an "alibi,"
但我们都知道以西结被杀 她脱不了干系
we all know she had something to do with Ezekiel's murder.
这是一场善与恶的神圣战争 伙计们
This is a biblical war of good versus evil, folks.
我要对星光追随者们进行全面猎杀
And I'm declaring hunting season on Starlighters.
撒旦 婴儿杀手
谈到婴儿杀手的话题 有请嘉宾多里恩布恩博士
Now, on the subject of baby-killers, let's welcome our guest Dr. Dorian Boone.
被她谋杀时 她的宝宝有什么感觉
Dr. Boone, what'd Starlight's baby feel when she murdered it?
傻逼自由党成员的安全空间
为以西结寻求正义
撒马利亚人怀抱大学 完成了一项针对雪貂的研究
There was a study done at Samaritan's Embrace University
鞭炮派我来的
证明了未出生的婴儿 早在受孕时就有痛感了
on ferrets which proves unborn babies feel pain as early as conception.
英雄克星
第四季第五集
本WEB版外挂字幕由  风吹来的那片云  双语合并
她要在家待两个星期 我要怎么办 马文
What am I supposed to do with her home for two weeks, Marvin?
我有工作要做
I have a job.
- 我也有工作 - 而且 那个男孩需要缝针
- So do I. - And the boy needed stitches,
我们肯定得付钱 这点你可以肯定
which you can be sure we're going to get the bill for.
宝贝 居然因为打架被停学
Suspended for fighting, baby?
- 这可不像你 - 爸 我...
- This ain't like you. - Dad, I--
你当时是怎么想的
What were you thinking?
他说祖国人是英雄 我就告诉他真相了
He said Homelander's a hero, so I told him the truth.
然后 他让我滚蛋 我就打了他
Then he told me to f-word off, so I hit him!
宝贝 不能用打架解决问题
Baby, fighting is not how you solve problems.
为什么  你不就是这么解决问题的吗
Why not? That's what you do.
亲爱的 回你房间去
Sweetie, go to your room.
回你房间去
Go to your room!
- 好吧 莫妮克... - 该死的 马文
- Okay, Monique... - Goddamn it, Marvin.
我绝不会因为超级英雄这种事 再失去一个心爱之人了
I am not gonna lose another person I love to this superhero shit.
- 我去跟她谈谈 - 你把这事处理好
- Let me talk to her. - You fix this.
马上就去
Now.
咱能别这么神神秘秘的吗  这里太他妈冷了
Fuck all this cloak and dagger shite. It's bloody freezing out here.
我本想去你妈暖和的阴户里见面
Well, I mean, I was thinking we could meet in your mom's pussy,
可惜你妈那里“游人如织”
but, you know, I wanted someplace more private.
那你有什么想法
So, what you thinking?
布彻尔 听着
Butcher, listen.
这次我们来干怎么样
How about we do this job,
就我们俩
just you and me?
我不知道 乔 有点突然 不是吗
I don't know, Joe. It's a bit all of a sudden, isn't it?
比利 你那个团队一点不中用
Billy... your team is a joke.
你以为我没注意到吗
You think I haven't noticed?
母乳就快崩溃了 法兰奇他妈的是个瘾君子
M.M.'s on the verge of a breakdown, Frenchie's a fucking junkie,
休伊胆小如鼠 那两位超人类
Hughie is a gaping wet pussy. And the two Supes on your side?
出于某种原因 对她们俩的问题 你就是个睁眼瞎
Man, for whatever reason, you have a blind spot for them.
好吧 星光可能有问题
All right, I'll give you Starlight.
但喜美子是把“好枪”
But Kimiko's a bloody good weapon,
另外 其他成员还是可以的
and the rest of them are still up to scratch.
我真不理解你的想法 真不理解
Well, I don't get you. I don't.
明明一半大脑已经长满了肿瘤
Half your brain is a fucking tumor.
本可以将祖国人一击毙命的时候 你却打了退堂鼓
This is your last shot at Homelander, and now you decide to go soft?
他们确实都是正派的人
Yeah, they are decent people,
但你我与正派无缘
but you and me,
我的生活 去他妈的
we don't belong with decent.
科林呢
Hey, so, where is Colin?
不知道 为什么问起他
Chais pas. Why?
因为他一声不吭就不见了踪影
Because he completely ghosted me.
你们闹矛盾了吗
Did you guys get into a fight or something?
他出城了 连再见都没说
He, uh, went out of town last-minute.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
好极了
Super.
你好吗
How are you?
很好
So great.
他妈的 这里跟个停尸房似的 怎么都拉着张大长脸
Fucking hell, it's like a morgue in here. What's with all the long faces?
谁知道 也许是因为 你杀了人 我却要背黑锅
I don't know, maybe because I'm getting blamed for the murder you did.
我想叫你贱屄 可你不具备那种深度或温暖
I'd call you a cunt, but you ain't got the depth or the warmth.
我一直想问你来着
I've been meaning to ask you something.
你是怎么干掉以西结的
How was it that you took out Ezekiel?
我不知道
I have no idea.
胡说
Bullshit.
真的 我眼前一黑就失去了意识 醒过来时 他已经挂了
God's honest. I, uh... blacked out, came to, and there he was.
在拖车里“无处不在”
All over the shop.
不过 别管那件屁事了 因为我已经找到它了
But never mind that bollocks because, my son, I have found it--
我们企盼的解决方法
the answer to all our prayers.
什么解决方法
And what might that be?
没什么大不了的 只是一种杀死超人类的病毒罢了
Ah, it's nothing much. Just a... a virus that kills Supes.
哪有这种东西
Such a thing does not exist.
之前是没有 但现在有了
Did not exist. Does now.
戈多尔金大学的聪明混蛋
You see, some clever cunts over at Godolkin University cooked up a bug
搞出了某种 能附着在他们血液里五号上的病毒
that latches onto the V in their bloodstream.
对人类完全无害 但对超人类
Now, it's completely harmless to humans, but to Supes?
就是他妈的恶魔了
Fucking diabolical.
那要是给我和喜美子注射了 我们就会翘辫子
So, you shove this shit into me and Kimiko and we just... drop dead?
对 就是这个意思
Yep. That's the idea.
它的强度还不足以杀死祖国人
Now, it ain't juiced enough to kill Homelander.
我想这么着 去弄来些 在可爱的当选副总统身上小试牛刀
But I reckon we get our hands on some and try it out on our lovely V.P. elect.
我们怎么现在才听说这事 布彻尔
And why the hell are we just finding out about this shit, Butcher?
因为出了个小岔子
There's only one small snag.
我去大学搞试剂时 纽曼先我一步得手
When I went to God U to nick it,
所以 我们得从她手里抢回来
Neuman had pipped me to the post, so we're gonna have to nick it from her.
即使对你来说 这也未免太疯狂 太穷途末路了
This is insane and desperate. Even for you.
疯狂地走在穷途末路上 这正是我们的境地 你不觉得吗
Well, insanely desperate's where we are, don't you think, love?
好啦 别争了
Okay. All right, all right. Time out.
如果这种病毒像布彻尔说得那么危险
Look, if this virus is as dangerous as Butcher says it is,
你真的希望它落入纽曼手中吗
do you really want it in Neuman's hands?
不 你说得对
No. No, you're right.
这下搞明白了
All right, then. Then we're sorted.
还有件很小很小的事
Oh, uh, uh... One other tiny little thing.
我需要你去给我们搞份总统特赦令
I need you to get us one presidential pardon.
主啊 他们邀请我加入超级七人队
Lord, they asked me to join The Seven.
我知道应该开心
I know I should be happy,
可要去对抗所有的罪人 我不确定自己够不够坚强
but I'm not sure I'm strong enough to fight all the sinners.
你会护佑我吗 耶稣 你...你在吗
Will you carry me, Jesus? Are you... are you there?
鞭炮 耶和华的士兵
新演播部门沃特信仰 摄制了刚才那段视频
That clip is from our new studio division Vought Faith.
说到信仰 一起来默哀片刻
Speaking of faith,
追悼我的基督徒兄弟以西结 一路走好 朋友
let's all have a moment of silence for my brother in Christ, Ezekiel. Adios, amigo.
缅怀以西结
你...你还好吗
You, um, you all right?
还在找泄露消息的人
Still searching for this leak.
有线索吗
Any leads?
我正在查
Working on it.
肯定是有人泄露出去的
But it's got to be someone.
那段录像不是自己跑出犯罪分析部的 我说得对吗
That footage didn't just run itself out of Crime Analytics, am I right?
有我能帮上忙的 尽管说
Let me know if I can help.
真他妈的 你身上有跳蚤还是怎么着
For fuck's sakes. You got fleas or something?
别走远 多米尼克 不会花很长时间的
Stay close, Dominic. This won't take long.
先生们 我十分钟后要上陶艺课
Gentlemen... I have pottery class in ten minutes.
你是想去捏粘土 还是
Would you rather finger some fucking clay or...
史丹福德艾德加 全面无条件赦免
想他妈的离开这里
...walk the fuck out of here?
他可真他妈的感激不尽 不是吗
Fuck, really grateful cunt, isn't he?
懂点礼貌不行吗
Where's your fucking manners?
今天不是我的生日 这也并不是礼物
It's not my birthday, and this is not a gift.
维多利亚纽曼有我们需要的东西
Victoria Neuman has something we need.
某种病毒
Some kind of... virus.
- 我不明白你的意思 - 得了吧 小史丹
- I have no idea what you mean. - Come on, Stanny.
在我看来
You struck me as the type of bloke
你是为达目的不择手段的人
what keeps his paws in all sorts of dirty little pies.
你帮我们从纽曼手里搞来这个病毒
Look, you help us get this virus from Neuman,
我们就帮你离开这里
we'll help you get the fuck out of here.
让我参与针对维多利亚的阴谋 你们一定是到了穷途末路的境地
You must be pretty desperate to try and enlist me in a plot against Victoria.
对我来说 她就像亲女儿一样
She is like a daughter to me.
出卖了你的女儿
Yeah, a daughter who sold you out.
我就是这样培养她的
She did what I raised her to do.
没错 你把她调教成了怪物 却没想调教她的小女儿
You're right, you taught her how to be a monster, but not her little girl.
你不知道
You didn't know?
她给可爱的小佐伊注射了五号
She shot up sweet little Zoe full of V.
把自己的女儿 变成了嘴里吐触手的怪物
Turned her into a tentacle-mouthed nightmare.
我们让你离开这里怎么样 无罪释放
How about we get you out of here,
还会让你得到佐伊的监护权
exonerated and throw in custody of Zoe?
这桩交易再好不过了 你心里清楚
There ain't no better deal. And you know it.
得承认这一点 这混蛋穿西装真他妈的有范儿
Got to hand it to him... cunt knows how to wear a whistle.
这是个坏主意
This is a bad idea.
星光 真是让人喜出望外啊
Starlight. What an unexpected pleasure.
我一直觉得跟你很亲近
You know, I've always felt a certain kinship with you.
- 我们要去哪  - 往西走
- Where we headed? - West.
真有品味 有毛巾给我铺在座位上吗
Charming. Do you have a towel I could place over the seat?
- 我们的蜜月绝对是场灾难 - 才不是呢
- Absolute disaster, the-the-- our honeymoon. - It wasn't a disaster.
- 拜托 严肃点 - 阿卡普尔科没那么糟糕
- Come on! Be serious. - Acapulco wasn't that bad.
- 蜜月套房有两张单人床 - 是的
- The honeymoon suite had two twin beds. - Yeah.
还有人在池畔酒吧呕吐
There were people vomiting at the-the swim-up bar...
全包自助餐似乎只包括沙门氏菌
and the all-included buffet seemingly only included salmonella.
既然这么讨厌分时度假 为什么还花钱预定
If you hated it so much, why did you buy a timeshare?
- 他预定的 - 因为那家伙...
- He bought a timeshare. - 'Cause that guy...
那家伙强行推销给我的
That guy put the hard sell on me.
- 如果能回到过去就好了 不是吗  - 是的
- It'd be great to go back, wouldn't it? - Yeah.
回去体验食物中毒吗
For the food poisoning?
不 就...去阿卡普尔科 知道吗
No, to... just to Acapulco, you know?
去布兰森和皮金福奇
To... go to Branson and-and Pigeon Forge.
巴黎 我一直都想去巴黎
Oh, Paris, I have always wanted to go to Paris.
我还不知道呢
- I never knew that. - Yeah.
有项徒步旅行
They have this walking tour
带你去《达芬奇密码》中 提及的所有地方
that goes to all the spots in The Da Vinci Code.
- 我知道 - 想象一下吧
- Yeah. - Imagine that.
我知道
Yeah, wow. Wow, I'd, uh...
我可不想错过
I'd hate to miss it.
这倒提醒我了
That reminds me,
我想给你这个 休伊
I want to give you... this,
这是我的订婚戒指
Hughie, which is my engagement ring
用它向安妮求婚吧
for when you propose to Annie.
妈妈 太...谢谢你了 太贴心了 但我不...我不知道是否...
Wow, Mom. Uh... Thank you, that's so sweet, but I-I don't, I don't know if, um,
- 我不知道我们是否准备好结婚了 - 你疯了吗
- I don't know if we're ready,  like, right now-- - Are you crazy?
- 快拿去吧 你个白痴 - 好的
- Lock that shit down, you moron. - Okay.
谢谢
Thank you.
我知道我不能...
You know, I can't, um...
改变任何事情 但是
you know, change anything, but...
我真的...
I'm really sor...
错过了这个 我真的很遗憾
I'm really sorry that I missed this.
错过了家庭时光
You know, this.
我也是
Me, too.
我知道你尝试过联系休伊
And look, I-I-I know you tried to reach out to Hughie,
我不应该阻断你们之间的联系
and I should never have kept you away.
没...
It's...
我要...去趟卫生间
I'm gonna-- I'm gonna go to the ladies' room.
没问题 你还好吗
Oh, you okay?
怎么了
What is it?
- 你居然给了她授权  - 我知道...
- You gave her power of attorney. - I knew--
你很多年都没见到她了 你是以为我应付不了吗
You haven't seen her in years. Did you think I couldn't handle it?
不是的 我...
It's not that.
你还记得加加得白血病那次吗
You remember when Jar Jar got leukemia?
记得
Yeah.
那只猫不肯吃东西 但不知怎么的 它仍然有东西可拉
Cat wouldn't eat, and yet somehow still had diarrhea,
你不让我给它做安乐死
and you would not let me put him down,
直到最终 它体内...
until he eventually kind of just, you know, exploded--
充满了血和屎 是的 我记得
With blood and shit. Yeah, I remember.
- 对 - 但我那时才九岁
- Right. - But I was nine.
你跟那时一样
You are still the same little kid.
你不肯让任何人离去
You hold on tight to everyone.
我爱你这一点
And I love you for that,
但是 知道吧
but... you know,
涉及到医疗事前指示时
when it came to, uh, an advanced directive...
这么说吧 我不想像加加那样死去
Let's just say I didn't want to end up like Jar Jar.
- 你妈呢  - 去卫生间了 记得吗
- Hey, where's your mom gone? - Uh, she went to the bathroom, remember?
记得 当然记得
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
这里真不错
You got a nice place.
我很少来这里
I've rarely been.
气味难闻
It's the smell.
但如果维多利亚想避人耳目 肯定会来这里
But if Victoria wanted to keep her proclivities quiet, it'd be here.
这是在搞什么
What is all this?
我和你们一样惊讶
I'm as surprised as you are.
毛球先生
临时五号
你找到了什么
What'd you find?
我没找到的才重要
It's what I did not.
看 标签标记了该病毒的每次迭代
See, the labels mark each iteration of this virus.
有人正在进行测试 但现在...
Somebody's been running tests, but now...
试剂都不见了
...it's all gone.
什么
What?
天哪
Holy shit.
该死的贱人
Fucking bitch.
- 别动手 - 维多利亚 你神清气爽啊
- Easy. - Victoria. You're looking well.
以为你出狱的事 我会不知情
You think I wouldn't know the minute you and your ankle monitor stepped out of that prison?
我不记得允许过你 把我的娱乐室变成病毒学实验室
I don't recall giving you permission to turn my rec room into a virology lab.
你居然把这些混蛋带到这里来了
You brought these assholes here?
- 他们想杀了我 - 对不起
- They want to kill me. - I'm sorry.
你是因为我背叛你而生气吗
Are you upset that I betrayed you?
你们两个别闹了 这不是什么家庭闹剧
Oi, knock it off, you two. This ain't Family Pies.
给你们五秒钟 告诉我你们对萨米尔做了什么
You have five seconds to tell me what you did to Sameer,
- 不然我就让你们血染满墙 - 萨米尔是哪位
- or I paint this fucking room red. - Who the fuck's Sameer?
够了
Enough.
你让萨米尔加入了 聪明
So, you brought in Sameer. Smart.
我也会那么做
That's what I'd have done.
但无论他发生了什么事 都不是我们做的
But whatever happened to him, it wasn't us.
我们应该一起找到他
We should find him together.
别他妈的跟我开玩笑了
You're fucking kidding me.
要是我没想错 你伤害他们
If I'm not mistaken, you hurt these people,
他们就会揭露 你超人类杀手的真面目 是吗
they expose you as a super-abled killer, yes?
那恐怕我们就陷入僵局了
Then I'm afraid that we are at a stalemate.
你不妨利用他们的专业知识
You might as well use their expertise.
至少 他们当炮灰还是合格的
At the very least, they're effective cannon fodder.
谢谢 你可真是太好心了
Thanks. That's really nice of you.
一个故事 讲述英雄
A story about a hero...
我不会放弃你 但你不能放弃自己
I'm not giving up on you, and you can't give up on yourself.
以及受他指导的跑步选手
...and the boy he taught to run.
跑得再快些
Run faster than that!
- 我放弃  - 别放我鸽子
- I quit. - Don't you bail on me!
伙计 离我远点
Get off of me!
要么克服困难 好好活下去 要么害自己早早进入坟墓
You can outrun this life, or you can run yourself into an early grave.
《训练火车头》
谢谢 多谢
Thank you, thank you.
相信我 对于这部电影 我和你们一样兴奋 它...
Trust me. I'm just as excited as you all for this film, that is...
是我心爱的电影
...so close to my heart.
伙计 也许是我感觉有误 但我觉得气氛有些紧张
Hey, listen, man. Call me crazy, but I'm sensing a little tension here.
有什么不对劲吗
Anything wrong?
有 老兄
Yeah, dude.
你他妈的报道了
You fucking reported
我丢掉犯罪分析部主管的职位
that I got shitcanned as head of Crime Analytics.
我很抱歉 但...
I'm sorry, but...
如果我要显得公正和平衡
Look, I got to take a couple of shots at the home team now and again,
偶尔也得对自家人下手
if I'm gonna appear fair and balanced.
我会撤回那些话
Look, I'll make a retraction.
太晚了 已经覆水难收了
No. It's way too late for that shit.
诺亚鲍姆巴赫 撤掉了我在他新剧中的角色
Noah Baumbach pulled me from his latest slice-of-life drama.
对不起 伙计 我不知道该说什么
I'm sorry, man, I don't know what to say.
这不是个人恩怨
You know, it wasn't personal.
一定要看我演的 沃特优选频道的惊悚片《双重标准》
Be sure to check me out in the Vought+ thriller, Double Standard,
刚刚重新拍摄完重新拍摄
which just finished reshooting its reshoots,
那么多次的重拍让它 成了有史以来耗资最高的电视节目
making it the most expensive TV show ever.
所以肯定很精彩 我说得对吗
So, you know, it's got to be good, am I right?
火车头
A-Train!
在沃特历史上 这还是第一次
For the first time in Vought's history,
在超级七人队中有两位黑人英雄 还有一位种族不明确的英雄
we have two Black heroes in The Seven and one unspecified.
是的 好棒
Yeah. Wow.
沃特自豪地支持 黑人 原住民 有色人种 为其发声
Vought proudly supports and amplifies BIPOC voices.
- 不是吗 卡梅隆  - 确实如此 深海
- Isn't that right, Cameron? - It sure is, Deep.
正因为这样 善于表达的英雄们
Which is why these articulate heroes
将领导沃特最新的多元化倡议
will lead Vought's newest diversity initiative.
“黑人动力”
Black At It.
有人说:“觉醒 不惜失去顾客” 我们说:“觉醒 抗争种族不公正”
Some say, "Go woke, go broke." Well, we say, "Go woke, get yoked."
作为创新计划的一部分 针对多元化的受众
And as part of our new initiative, we'll be debuting a new feature,
我们将推出一项特色服务
specifically for our diverse audiences.
定制数字产品植入
Custom digital product placement.
请看本人三度获得
Check this out, here we have a clip
音乐电视奖的作品《涨潮》的视频
from my three-time MTV Award winner Rising Tide.
看 白人用流媒体观看的话
Get this, when a white fan streams my movie,
就会看到我拿着根据他们品味 而量身定制的品牌产品
they'll see me holding a brand tailor-made to their tastes.
要是黑人用流媒体观看呢
And then, you know, if a Black fan streams it,
就会看到美味的沃特帝国桃子干邑
they'll see a delicious Vought Imperial Peach Cognac.
很酷
Ooh, it's pretty cool.
好 那么
All right, so,
卡梅隆和深海的一番介绍之后
chuffa, chuffa from Cameron and Deep.
我们就宣布 莱恩的处女作《超人类学校》
Then we announce Ryan's debut series, Super School.
- 最后选了这个标题  - 只有这个获得了批准
- That's the title we went with? - That was the only thing we got cleared.
镜头会转向我 对吗  我要开始谈拍摄初衷之类的
Then they're gonna throw to me, right? For my little "why now" moment.
解释我是如何从
You know, how I got my inspo
教导下一代超人类的过程中获得灵感
from my time really teaching the next generation of super-powered youth,
你这时上场 亲爱的 对吧  到时候你坐到我身边
and then it's go time, baby, right? That's when you're gonna come out to me,
进行两个小时的问答环节
and we do, like, a little two-hour Q and A.
邦妮 顺便一提 你今天很漂亮
Bonnie, you look gorgeous today, by the way.
- 你收到我的短信了吗  - 收到了
- Did you get my text? - Yeah.
是叫我们了吗 告诉他们 我们15 20分钟后就上台
Right. Is that for us? Listen, tell 'em we'll be out in like 15, 20, okay?
- 好的 - 很好
- Okay. - All right, cool.
莱恩 你觉得如何
Hey, Ryan, what do you think?
说真的 你觉得怎么样  我真的很想知道
Seriously. What do you think? I-I really want to know.
就是...
It's just...
《超人类学校》
I mean, Super School?
我们为什么要拍青少年节目
Why are we doing a teen show, anyway?
因为我们喜欢钱
Um, 'cause we like money.
如果不想 就别拍
If you don't want to do it...don't.
不要拍 我说真的
Don't do it. I mean it.
我要扮“坏人” 斗胆进几句“忠言”
I'm just gonna pop the horns up here a little bit
还有一个月就开拍了
and play devil's advocate. We are a month away from shooting.
所有布景都搭建好了 还为多伦多一半的摄影棚交了费
Built all the sets. I think we bought up half the sound stages in Toronto.
谁在乎
Who cares?
这是因为 我在敏卡凯利面前手淫了吗
Is this because I jerked it in front of Minka Kelly?
那次是误会
Because, again, that was just crossed wires.
天啊 怎么做才能激发起你的兴致
Hey, guy, what's it gonna take to get you amped?
想要被列为制片人 没问题
Do you want a E.P. credit? That is done.
想批准剧本 我什么都可以...
You want to get script approval? I can make anything sing--
把你的美国运通黑卡给他
Give him your black Amex.
什么 你想要...这样吧
What? You want... You know what?
我的钱包都给你好了
Why don't you take my whole wallet.
还有你捷豹车的钥匙
And the keys to your Jaguar.
乐意至极
I would love... to do that.
莱恩 你觉得如何
Ryan, what do you say?
不要
No.
好吧
Yeah.
那么 你...真的没有生我的气吗
So, you're... you're really not mad at me?
不 我为你感到骄傲 因为你说出了自己的想法
No. I'm proud of you for speaking your mind.
莱恩
Ryan...
我这一辈子都在被人操纵
I've been, uh... manipulated by people my whole life.
别人告诉我要说什么 要站在哪里
Being told what to say, where to stand.
就像个奴隶 甚至更糟
It-It's like being a slave, only worse.
我做了一些反思
I did some reflecting,
我意识到 我也一直在对你做同样的事情
and I realized that I've been doing the same thing to you.
但以后不会了
But no more.
今后 我们俩都不再遵循规则
From now on, no more rules. For either of us.
我们都不再受他人的奴役
We are both emancipated from slavery.
我们是自由的
We're free.
- 好吧  - 是的 我知道
- Sound good? - Yeah.
是吧
Yeah?
儿子 我只在乎你的想法 别人的想法 我才不在乎
Oh, buddy, I-I don't care what anyone else thinks but you.
对我而言 除了你我之外 整个星球
Far as I'm concerned, this whole planet is empty.
只是一片虚无而已
Except for you and me.
明明有60多双鞋 却偏偏穿了这双来
As if you don't have 60 more pairs.
这双是安德鲁王子送给我的
Prince Andrew gave me these shoes.
我突然想起自己是多么讨厌这里
I'm suddenly reminded of how much I hated it here.
真的吗 我曾经很喜欢这里
Really? I used to love it.
在这里总感觉更自由一些
I always felt a little more free here.
然而你却把我的农场变成了 传染病实验室
And yet you've turned my farm into an infectious disease lab.
没人
Clear.
我只能假设你正在 寻找控制祖国人的方法
I can only assume that you're searching for a way to control Homelander.
他就是弗洛伊德描述的随机冲动 和严重不安全感的糟糕组合
You know, he's a Freudian cesspool of random impulse and deep insecurity.
没有人可以控制那种人
There's no one who can control that.
你让自己和佐伊陷入了可怕的危险
You've put yourself and Zoe in terrible danger.
不 是你让我和佐伊 陷入了可怕的危险
No. You put me and Zoe in terrible danger.
你就像利用其他人一样利用我 必须有人保护她
You used me like you use everybody else. Somebody had to protect her.
你是说给她注射五号化合物
You mean shooting her up with Compound V.
你把一个明眸善睐的热情女孩 变成了...
You took a bright-eyed little girl, and you turned her into a--
变成了什么 一个怪物
Into a what? A monster?
所以你才让我隐藏自己的真实身份
Is that why you had me hide what I was?
待在阴影里 永远别爬太高
Stick to the shadows, never reach too high?
那是为了保护你
That was to protect you.
不 那是因为你觉得 我给你带来了羞耻
No, that was because you were ashamed of me.
我女儿永远不必那样生活
My daughter will never have to live like that.
我们找到病毒 这次短暂的休战结束时会怎样
So, what's gonna happen when we find the virus and this little truce is over?
星光让她睁不开眼
Starlight blinds the bitch,
在她搞清楚状况之前 我就给她注射一剂
before she knows what's what, I'll jab her with a dose.
好的
Okay.
我找到了一个受伤的人
We've got a casualty.
那是萨米尔吗
Is that Sameer?
不是 这是他的一位实验室助理
No, it's one of his lab assistants.
这他妈的是什么...
What the hell is--
天哪
注射过五号的鸡
V'd-up fucking chicken!
去他妈的
Fuck this.
你本可以警告我们 你那位叫萨米尔的朋友
Well, you could've warned us your pal Sameer
给鸡群注射了五号 让它们搞大屠杀 不是吗
was V-ing up a Kentucky Fried fucking massacre, couldn't ya?
我不知道 好吗 显然出了什么问题
I didn't know, okay? Something obviously went wrong.
- 我们必须找到他 - 可不是嘛
- We have to find him. Yeah, right.
我们相信你才怪
And we're supposed to believe you?
撒谎对你来说跟吃饭睡觉一样 稀松平常 不是吗
You eat, sleep and shit lies, don't you?
你是美德典范 行了吧  你告诉朋友们那个交易了吗
Right, 'cause you're such a paragon of virtue. You tell your friends about the deal we made?
等等 这话什么意思
Wait, wh-what does that mean?
他说会偷走你们手上掌握的 所有关于我的文件
Said he'd steal all your files you had on me
只要我给他莱恩
if I gave him Ryan.
他妈的开什么玩笑
Are you fucking kidding me?
可我并没有偷 不是吗  那就证明我是真诚的
And I didn't go through with it, did I? Which proves I'm on the level.
我们什么时候才能长点教训  他他妈的就是狗改不了吃屎
When are we gonna learn? He's never gonna fucking change.
我们还要进行大面积搜索
All right, listen. We got a lot of ground to cover,
还是去找人吧
so let's just go.
你们活了这么久 我觉得这绝对是个奇迹
It's an absolute wonder to me that you've all managed to live this long.
怎么了 我没有偷呀
What? I didn't go through with it.
真好
Ooh, that's nice.
不好意思 嗨
Excuse me. Hi.
我允许你把振动蓝牙肛珠 拿出来了吗
Did I say you could take out your vibrating Bluetooth anal beads?
现在就把它们放回去
- Go pop them back in right now.
这是一次重要的活动
This is an important event.
你真希望我在舞台上 当着我们死忠粉丝的面射精吗
You really expect me to come onstage in front of our most loyal fans?
对 我想让每个人都知道
Oh, yeah. I want everyone to know
你是个闻我阴屁的贱货
what a grubby little queef-sniffer you are.
抱歉 我本来没打算 在这种场合告诉你这件事
I'm sorry. This wasn't how I was planning to tell you,
但你那一套对我来说不管用了
but, um, this isn't working out for me anymore.
我是说 你掌握实权时是一回事
I mean, it was one thing when you were really in charge around here,
但现在不是那么回事了...
but now, I mean...
你...这是要甩了我
You... are dumping me?
要我当奴可以 但我的主
必须得真正地掌握实权 知道吧
I need a dom who's dominating. You know?
但我希望我们仍然可以做朋友
But, uh, I hope we can still be friends.
你是生气时就这副样子 还是星光打烂了你的脸
Is this your angry look, or did Starlight fuck up your face?
要不是你这贱人在辅佐祖国人
You know, if you weren't Homelander's right-hand bitch,
我肯定会带你去个隐秘的地方 好好教训你一顿
I'd take you out behind the woodshed and whup your ass.
听起来很符合你的一贯作风
Mm, sounds on-brand.
你陷害我 让我挨打
You set me up to get my ass beat.
而你却正中了我的“下怀”
And you fell for it.
不过 你现在不用装成受害者了 你就是受害者
But, hey, now you don't have to play a victim. You can really be one.
你们都觉得 我是愚蠢 贫困的下等白人
Y'all just think I'm stupid poor white trash.
我没认为你贫困啊
I don't think you're poor.
随心所欲地低估我好了
Underestimate me all you want.
让我给你背后捅刀子变得更容易了
Makes it that much easier to stick a fucking shiv in your back.
法兰奇还好吗
Frenchie okay?
他不肯告诉我 你去问他
你还好吗
Are you okay?
我注意到你有一点投射功能障碍
I noticed you're having a little, uh... projectile dysfunction.
不如这样吧 你操心自己的事就好了
Yeah, you know what? Why don't you worry about yourself, okay?
我是呀 如果超能力出了问题 你对我们就没多大用处了
I am. You're not much use to us if your powers are on the fuckin' fritz.
在国家电视台上 看到了你把鞭炮打得屁滚尿流
Saw you beat the piss out of Firecracker on national television.
别误会我的意思 我很享受那个场面
Don't get me wrong, I enjoyed the hell out of it, but, um,
但你不认为自己有点失控吗
don't you think it was a little... out of control?
我们不能轻易丧失冷静
We can't lose our cool like that.
“我们”
We?
拜托 安妮 只有我才懂你的处境
Come on, Annie. I'm one of the only people who does get it.
双重身份
Dual identities.
我还是娜迪亚
I'm still Nadia.
你以为我不想时不时地做娜迪亚吗  但我不能
You think I don't want to let her out sometimes? But I can't.
我得做纽曼
I got to be Neuman.
妈的 你当星光当了这么久
And, shit, you've been Starlight for so long,
还知道安妮是谁吗
do you even know who Annie is anymore?
你的情绪控制得真好
Yeah, you really got your shit locked down.
女士们 先生们 有请泰克骑士
Ladies and gentlemen, Tek-Knight.
《泰克骑士》
拍完上一部电影后已经过去一整年了
It's been a whole year since my last movie,
所以 我觉得我们应该整装待发
so I'd say we're due for a reboot.
不 眼睛向前看 别让他们看到我们在说话
No, keep your eyes forward. Don't let them see us talking.
- 谁  - 智者 祖国人 他们所有人
- Who? - Sage. Homelander. All of them.
天哪 你是吸了冰毒吗
Oh, God. Are you on meth?
记得我们说过会互相帮助吗
Remember when we said we'd help each other?
泄密者不是阿妮卡 而是我
The leak wasn't Anika. It was me.
搞什么鬼
What the fuck?
- 搞什么鬼 你他妈的找死吗  - 冷静点 艾诗丽
- Are you fucking suicidal? - Just chill out, Ashley.
冷静 你害我成了他妈的同谋 你个混蛋
Chill out? You just made me a fucking accomplice, you piece of shit.
我在祖国人的厕所里拉了一泡屎而已
I took one shit in Homelander's toilet.
我才不会加入叛军联盟 我得告诉他
I'm not joining the fucking Rebel Alliance. I need to tell him.
你不止是拉了一泡屎而已 我们俩都心知肚明
Hey. You've done a lot more than just take a shit, and we both know that.
我们达成了协议
We made a deal,
所以 你要么帮我摆脱智者的追查
so you either help me get Sage off my jock,
要么跟我一起玩完
or you go down with me.
《泰克骑士》以前所未有的深度 探索人性的黑暗
The Tek-Knight plumbs a whole new pit of darkness.
用涅槃乐队的热门歌曲配乐
With its soundtrack of Nirvana hits
有12分钟的镜头 都处于一片漆黑之中
and a 12-minute sequence that's entirely pitch-black.
找到了 可能只有这一瓶猕猴桃无糖...
I found it, possibly the only bottle of Diet Kiwi S...
- 爸爸呢  - 我以为他和你在一起
- Where's Dad? - I thought he was with you.
- 没有吗  - 没有
- No? - No.
爸
Dad?
- 休  - 爸
- Hugh? - Dad?
爸
Dad?
休
Hugh?
爸
Dad.
- 休  - 等等 站在这里等一下
- Hugh? - Wait, wait, wait, wait. Just wait here for a second.
爸
Hey, Dad.
怎么会这样
How'd that happen?
休伊 发生了什么事
Hughie, what's going on?
我不知道 我...
I do-- I don't know. I don't know what...
把它放下来吧 不如你...
Look, why don't you set that down and, uh, why don't you...
跟我来吧
why don't you come with me.
你是谁
Who are you?
爸 是...爸 是我 是休伊
Dad, it's... Dad, it's me. It's Hughie.
- 不好意思 - 女士
- Excuse me. - Uh, ma'am?
我的天哪 呼叫保安
Oh, my God. Call security!
呼叫保安 红色代码
Call security! Code red!
别这样 让我带你去吃晚饭吧
Don't be like that. Hey, let me take you to dinner.
我人很好的 我保证
Hey, I'm a nice guy, I promise.
我这是怎么了
What's-- what's happening to me?
请注意 有人报告发生紧急情况
Attention please. There has been a report of an emergency.
保持冷静 前往最近的出口 立即离开大楼
Proceed calmly to the nearest exit and leave the building immediately.
- 爸  - 休
- Dad? - Hugh?
- 妈的 - 休
- Oh, fuck. - Hugh?
- 爸  - 我得走了
- Dad? - I got to go.
等等 听我说 我可以解释 好吗
Yeah, wait, wait. Just listen, I can explain everything, all right?
不如你...跟我们一起走吧
Why don't-- why don't you just, uh, why don't you just come with us?
不行 对不起 我得带休伊去沃特公司商店
I can't, I'm sorry, I got to take Hughie to the Vought Company Store.
他正在攒钱 想买一个泰克骑士的娃娃
He's saving up for a Tek-Knight doll.
他说那是人偶 不过其实它就是个...娃娃
He-he-he calls it an action figure, but, you know, it's a-- it's a doll.
爸 我是休伊
Dad, I'm Hughie.
我就站在这里
I'm right here.
你才不是休伊呢 他11岁
You're not Hughie. He's 11.
休 我们回你房间去吧
Hugh? Why don't we go back to your room?
- 达芙妮  - 是的
- Daphne? - Yeah.
你怎么来了
Wh... what are you doing here?
你不应该在这里 你走了
You shouldn't be here. You left.
- 但我回来了 记得吗  - 是的
- But I came back. Remember? - Yeah.
我为你做了一切
I did everything for you,
可你完全不把我当回事 当我不存在
and you looked through me like I wasn't even there!
你毁了我的生活
You ruined my life.
毁了休伊的生活
Hughie's life.
爸 别说了
Dad, stop.
趴在地上 马上
Get down on the ground.
警官
Sir?
等等 不 不要
Wait. Wait. No! No, don't!
快 我们走
Let's go.
达芙妮
Daphne!
有请戈多尔金守护者 萨姆赖尔丹和凯特邓拉普
Please welcome the Guardians of Godolkin:
戈多尔金守护者
Sam Riordan and Cate Dunlap.
活动什么时候结束
Hey, how long's this thing supposed to go on for?
怎么 今晚有重要安排吗
Why, big plans tonight?
没什么 只是觉得 也许可以去干你妻子一炮
Nothing much, just gonna maybe fuck your wife.
- 什么  - 塔比莎想让我过去一趟
- Excuse me? - Tabitha. She wants me to swing by
一起深夜潜水 永远也不会停的那种
for a late-night muff-dive. Which'll take forever
因为我不需要浮出水面呼吸空气 我可以通过她的汁液呼吸
'cause I don't need to come up for air. I can just breathe right through her juices.
够了 我知道你那个 见不得光的八爪小贱人
Enough. I know about your little closeted eight-armed hand job machine.
我可以写份新闻稿 今晚之前就播出
I could cut a package together, have it on the air by tonight.
- 你不会那么做 - 试试看好了
- You wouldn't. - Watch me.
所以 安分守己点 好吗
So try and keep it classy, okay?
在搞笑的新喜剧《翻转》中联袂出演
...starring together in a hilarious new comedy, Flipped.
我是个自以为是的联谊会女孩 他是个书呆子
I'm a stuck-up sorority girl, he's a nerd,
但当吉普赛人将我们的身体互换...
but when a gypsy swaps our bodies...
那么 你想做什么
So, what do you want to do?
我们可以去买些热狗
We could go get some Nathan's Famous.
不 我是说宏伟蓝图 梦想 理想那些
No, I mean a little more boldly. I mean, like, big picture.
你想做什么
What do you... want to do?
你会嘲笑我的
You're gonna laugh at me.
不 我不会的
No, I won't.
我有点想帮助别人
I kind of want to help people.
但不是那种虚假的营救 而是真的帮助他们
But not like with fake saves, like really help.
我妈想要这样
It's what my mom would want.
了不起 太棒了
That's... amazing. That's great.
你想帮助她吗
You want to help her? Yeah?
- 想 但我... - 想帮 很好
- Yeah. But, I mean-- - Great.
亚当 你能让那位 可爱的年轻女士过来吗
Hey, Adam, will you send that lovely young lady over here, please?
你也过来
And you come, too.
他让你感觉不自在吗
...is he making you uncomfortable?
没事 你可以告诉我 你不会有麻烦的
No, you can tell me. You won't get in trouble.
有点
Kind of.
- 是的 - 莱恩
- Yeah. - Ryan?
你怎么想
What do you think?
亚当 我认为你应该道歉
Adam, I think you should apologize.
如果我行为不妥 我很抱歉
Uh, I'm sorry if I was inappropriate.
感觉你不是很真诚
Didn't seem like you meant it.
没有 我生来就是这种语气
Uh, yeah, that's just-- that's just my natural tone.
也许问题在于亚当看不起私人助理
Maybe the problem is that Adam is looking down on the P.A.
是的
Yeah.
Yeah, um...
亚当 我觉得你应该跪下来 再道一次歉
Adam, I think you should get on your knees and do it again.
如果我利用了我们之间 不对等的权力关系 我很抱歉
I'm sorry if I exploited our inequitable power dynamic,
我让你感到不自在了 请原谅我
and I made you feel uncomfortable. Please forgive me.
- 他还在撒谎 - 我同意
- He's still lying. - Mm-hmm. I agree.
我想 也许他需要点教训
I think maybe he needs to be taught a lesson.
我要你扇他一巴掌
I want you to slap him.
邦妮
Bonnie--
- 妈的 - 再来一巴掌
- Oh, fuck. - Do it again.
- 妈的 好吧 - 再来
- Okay... - Again.
我的天 疼死了
Homelander--Fuck me.
对不起 求你住手吧
I'm sorry. Stop, please.
莱恩 求你了
Bonnie, please. Please!
祖国人 妈的
- Homelander, pl--
拜托 我们可以休息一下吗
Please, can we take a break?
- 你没事吧  - 我很好
- Are you all right? - Yes, I'm all right.
我不知道你是天主教徒
I didn't know you were a Catholic.
很有戏剧性 不是吗
Something about the drama of it appeals. You know?
你还相信上帝吗
Do you still believe in God?
我想相信上帝
I want to.
只是
It's just, uh...
有时真是太难了
It's just so hard sometimes.
- 你呢  - 全心全意地相信
- And you? - With all my heart.
三位一体 复活 圣礼 全部都信
The trinity, the resurrection, the sacraments... all of it.
除了忏悔圣礼
Well, except for the Sacraments of Penance.
拜托 完全是胡扯
Come on. What a steaming pile of dog shit that is.
我真的觉得宽恕...
I really kind of think that forgiving is...
- 很重要 - 宽恕别人是很重要
- is important. - Forgiving, oui.
但被人宽恕就不是那么回事了
But not being forgiven.
我向某个素未谋面的牧师告罪
What, I confess to some priest I don't even know in a peep show booth,
所有的罪孽就都被洗净了
and all my sins wash away?
狗屁
Dog shit.
有些罪 上帝不应该宽恕
Some sins God should not forgive.
有些罪孽应该受到永恒的诅咒
Some sins deserve eternal damnation.
法兰奇
Frenchie...
你做了什么
...what have you done?
不止一件
It is not just one thing, you see.
我做了太多件坏事了
It is so many things.
你真的应该找人说说
You should really talk to someone.
真的 你告诉喜美子了吗
You should. I mean, have you told Kimiko?
如果我告诉她
If I tell her...
我害怕她会恨我
...I'm scared she'll hate me.
我更害怕她不会恨我
I'm even more scared she won't.
那是头该死的注射过五号的公牛吗
Is that a fucking V'd-up bull?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
慢慢地走开
Off we fuck, nice and slow.
太他妈疯狂了
This is fucking crazy.
跑
Run!
快
Come on. Go!
天哪
Oh, my God.
快
Come on.
快跑
Let's go!
这种事又发生在我身上 太他妈难以置信了
I can't believe this is fucking happening to me again.
天哪 萨米尔
Oh, my God, Sameer.
- 你还好吗  - 我很好 但...亨利
- Are you okay? - Yeah. I'm fine, but, uh, Henry...
等等 佐伊不在这里 是吗 因为...
Wait. Zoe's not here, is she? Because--
- 不 她没事 - 没事 好的
- No? No, no. She's okay. She's okay. - Okay, good.
等等 天哪 那是佐伊的爸爸吗
Wait. Oh, my God, is that Zoe's dad?
沙阿医生曾是 沃特研发中心的头号人物
Dr. Shah was my top man at Vought R&D
在他背着我剥夺我女儿的贞操之前
before he went behind my back and deflowered my daughter.
我那时20岁 早就已经失身了 现在并不是说这事的场合
Okay, I was 20, thoroughly deflowered, and this isn't the time or the place.
发生了什么
What happened?
我们给一只仓鼠注射了五号 好用它来测试病毒
We gave, uh, V to a hamster, so we could test the virus on it.
一只被注射过五号的仓鼠 这是你的第一个错误 我的朋友
Oh, a V'd-up hamster was your first mistake, mon ami.
它跑了 把实验室搞得一团糟
It got loose. Trashed the lab. We ran,
我们跑了出来 但五号已经泄漏进地下水了
but the V had already leaked into the ground water.
病毒没了吗
Is the virus gone?
- 对 - 该死
- Yes. - Fuck.
只剩下了...
Except for, uh...
只剩下了一剂
Except for one dose.
它的传播力有多强
Hey. How transmissible is that?
不是很强 只能通过体液 血液 唾液 精液传播
Not very. Only through bodily fluid. Blood, saliva... semen.
那我们将它注入你伙伴的尸体中 拿它当诱饵
Okay, so we inject it into your dead buddy over here as bait,
把尸体放到外面 去感染那些飞来飞去的羊
and then we put him outside to infect the crazy fucking flying sheep.
这家伙操不了羊啊
This man is in no condition to fuck a sheep.
羊会吃掉他
They would eat him.
胡扯 只剩这一剂了
Bollocks. That's the only dose.
- 我看还是带着它逃吧 - 布彻尔说得对 它太珍贵了
- I say we fucking leg it. - Butcher's right, it's too valuable.
跑的话 会有人跑不出去
Okay, we run, we don't all make it.
达尔文主义 亲爱的 不必跑得最快 不跑得最慢就行了
Darwinism, love. Don't got to be the fastest, just not the slowest.
- 一派胡言 - 够了 现在不要吵
- No fucking way. - Enough. Not now.
- 我不可能跑得比它们快 - 别听他编故事了
- I won't be able to outrun them. - Oh, don't you cry for that cunt.
他想把佐伊从你身边夺走 这就是他的全部计划 不是吗
He's just trying to nick Zoe from you. That's his whole fucking plan, isn't it?
- 他在撒谎 - 抱歉 小史丹 并不是在针对你
- He's lying. - Sorry, Stanny. Just business.
伙计们 别吵了
Guys, stop.
- 王八蛋 - 我早该知道的
- Son of a bitch. - I should've fucking known.
母乳可能会死 好吗  法兰奇也有可能
M.M. could die, okay? Or Frenchie.
你真的不在乎 被你推入虎口狼牙的是谁
I mean, you really don't care who you just throw to the wolves?
- 不是很在乎 - 你个怪物
- No, not really. - You're a monster,
我才不会让你做这种事
and I'm not letting you do this.
怎么 你要像胖揍鞭炮那样揍我吗
Or what? You gonna go stark raving like you did with Firecracker?
爆头女在我这边 何况你现在使不出超能力
I got the head popper and you can't even get it up.
够了 看
Enough. Enough! Look. Look.
都看到了吗 荨麻疹
Y'all see this? Hives.
我长了荨麻疹 因为你们这些混蛋快把我逼疯了
And I got them because y'all motherfuckers are driving me the fuck crazy.
安妮 你不能想冲谁发火就冲谁发火
Now, Annie, you can't just go around fucking everybody up.
纽曼 你真的想拿佐伊冒险
And, Neuman, do you really
让她被迫像你一样 在集体之家长大吗
want to risk Zoe growing up in a group home the way you did?
你
And you.
听着 我的宝贝女儿需要我
Look. My little baby girl needs me,
我还想去见她呢
and I intend on seeing her.
你不是怪物 布彻尔
You're not a monster, Butcher.
你是个混蛋 但你是个有心的混蛋
You are a motherfucker, but you a motherfucker with a heart.
那些人都是他杀的 他...那些人...
He killed those people. He... Those people.
给健康的人注射五号 就会发生疯狂的事
Yeah, crazy shit happens when you give healthy people V,
所以 我想一个人脑死亡时...
so I guess when someone's brain-dead...
- 你怎么这么冷静  - 我不是第一次
- H-How are you so calm? - This sort of isn't the first time
- 经历这种情况 - 你在找什么
- I've been through something like this. - What are you looking for?
我不知道 妥布霉素 拓扑替康 任何能让爸爸镇静的药物
I don't know. Tobramycin, topotecan, anything we can use to maybe slow Dad down.
如果我们没办到呢
Wait, w-what if we can't?
你不会有事的
Nothing is gonna happen to you.
达芙妮
Daphne!
你...你离开了我
You... you left me.
- 你离开了我们年幼的儿子 - 爸
- You left our little boy. - Dad.
- 你伤了我们的心 - 爸 别说了
- You broke our hearts. - Dad, stop.
休 求你了
Hugh, please.
- 休 求你了 - 我是休伊 爸
- Hugh, Hugh, please. Please, Hugh, please. - I'm Hughie, Dad.
你就是带我去了沃特商店
I'm the one you took to the Vought Store to buy the Tek-Knight doll.
我记得 尽管存了几个星期的钱 我还是缺八美元
Remember, I-I was, I was short eight bucks, even though I saved for weeks.
你说:“为了你的头号英雄 不惜一切”
And you said, "Anything for your number one hero."
但事情是这样的 爸 他从来都不是我的头号英雄
But that's the thing, Dad, he-he-he never was.
你才是
You are.
你是我的英雄
You're my hero.
所以我才需要你醒来
And that's why I-I needed you to wake up,
这样我就可以说出这句话 知道你听到了 我就放心了
so that I could say it, and I, and I, and I know that you heard it.
你是我的英雄 爸
You're my hero, Dad.
- 休伊  - 是的
- Hughie? - Yeah.
是的 爸 是我 是休伊
Yeah, Dad, it's me, it's me. It's Hughie.
我们在哪 这...
W-Where are we?
天哪 为什么...天哪 我为什么会... 我不知道发生了什么事
Oh, God, w... Oh, God. W-Why am I... I-I don't know what's going on.
- 说来话长 但... - 不
- It's-it's a long story, but-- - No! No!
爸...爸 是休伊 记得吗
Dad? Dad, it's Hughie. It's Hughie, remember?
我知道 我只是...我不...
I know. I-I know. I just, I-I don't...
我出了问题
There's-there's something wrong with me.
我...我无法阻止
I-I can't stop it.
我不知道该怎么办
I don't know what to do.
没关系
That's okay.
我想我知道该怎么办
I think I do.
你说病毒需要多长时间起效
How long did you say it takes for the virus to kick in?
每次都不一样
It's been different every time.
好吧
这可不妙
That's not good.
糟糕
Shit.
跑
Go, go, go! Go, go, go!
他妈的
Oh, shit.
萨米尔在哪里
Where's Sameer?
萨米尔在哪里 萨米尔
Where's Sameer? Sameer?
- 萨米尔 不 萨米尔在哪儿  - 维多利亚 冷静 就...
- Sameer! Sameer! Sameer! Where's Sameer? - Victoria. Victoria. Calm down. Just...
不 他在哪儿 萨米尔 我不知道
Where is he? We don't know...
萨米尔 不 他在哪儿
No, where is he?
不 萨米尔在哪里
No, where's Sameer?
你们食言了 这可不太好
Not very sporting of you to renege on a deal.
交易是用病毒换赦免
Deal was a pardon for the virus.
病毒没到手 就没有赦免
No virus? No deal.
我们搜查了农场 找不到沙阿博士
We scoured the property. We couldn't find Dr. Shah,
但我们发现了这个
but we did find this.
- 谢谢 - 我很抱歉
- Thank you. - I'm very sorry.
天哪 他妈的 你认真的吗
Jesus fucking Christ, are you serious?
成为英雄意味着什么
What does it mean to be a hero?
这个国家已经腐败不堪 无法修复
This country is corrupt beyond repair. So, we got to save it.
所以 我们必须拯救它 我们必须拯救美国
We have to save America.
我们必须为孩子们拯救世界
We have to save the world for our kids.
所以 我找你们来尽自己的一份力量
So, I'm reaching out to you, to do your part.
这么做并不容易
Now, it's not gonna be easy.
我们将被迫做出可怕的事情
We'll... We'll have to do some terrible things.
为了更大的利益做出
Some violent,
暴力 无情 甚至可能是残酷的事
merciless, maybe even cruel things, for the greater good.
那就是战争
That's war.
你们将不再是受人喜爱的名人
You'll no longer be beloved celebrities.
而是愤怒的众神
You will be wrathful gods.
时机成熟时
When the time comes...
你们会响应召唤吗
...will you answer the call?
我们怎么知道时机成熟了
How will we know when the time comes?
相信我 你们会知道的
Trust me, you'll know.
都听你的 祖国人
Anything you need, Homelander.
我们最近发现沃特塔里有人泄露消息
You see, we recently found a leak here at Vought Tower,
我想 我们可以一起解决这个问题
and I thought, together, we might plug it.
证据就在他的手机上 给马文米尔克打过电话
The proof was on his phone. Calls to Marvin Milk.
我不知道那是谁 我不知道马文米尔克是谁
I don't know who that is. I don't know who Marvin Milk is.
不是我干的 搞错了
I didn't do it. This is a mistake.
有人陷害我 我什么都没干
Someone set me up. Someone set me up. I didn't do anything.
拜托 伙计 我告诉你...
所以 爱国者们
So... A-Train.
让我见识一下你们的愤怒
Show me a little wrath.
今晚我仍然要干你妻子一炮
I'm still gonna fuck your wife tonight.
我们无法解决彼此的问题
但我们可以握着彼此的手
我们谈谈吧
不是这里
Not here.
- 请稍等 先生 - 警官
- Uh, just a moment, sir. - Madame, excusez-moi.
- 先生 我们会尽快帮助您 - 我犯下了谋杀罪
- Sir, we'll get to you when we can-- - I have committed murders.
好几起
Plural.
前台需要支援
There's a 10-13 at the front desk.
先生 把双手放在我能看到的地方
Sir, please put your hands where I can see them.
你怎么知道这会起作用
How do you know this is even gonna work?
我有一位法国人朋友
I-I have this, uh, French friend.
他教会了我很多关于药品的知识
He kind of taught me way too much about drugs.
如果我们不这样做 他的余生都会充满恐惧和困惑
Look, if we don't do this, then he spends the rest of his life scared and confused,
在监狱或疯人院中度过
in-in prison or-or an asylum.
或者他会杀掉更多无辜的人
Or he kills more innocent people.
他说得对
He's right.
休伊说得对 我不想成为加加
Hughie's right. I don't want to be Jar Jar.
不会疼的
It's not gonna hurt.
谢谢你
Thank you.
把儿子照顾得这么好
For taking such good care of our boy.
我保证我也会照顾好他
I promise I will do the same.
是的
Yeah.
发生了什么 我觉得...
What's happening? I feel...
- 好的 - 我...我很害怕
- Okay. - I'm-I'm-I'm scared.
爸 没事的 我就在这里
Hey, hey, Dad, it's okay. Hey. I'm right here.
我就在这里 我们都在
I'm right here. We both are.
我爱你 非常爱你
And I-I love you so much.
我接受你要离开 好吗 你放心走吧
I'm not gonna hold on, okay? You can go.
我也爱你 儿子
I love you, too, son.
我的小休伊
My wee Hughie.
- 你知道我真想去哪里吗  - 哪里
- Oh, y-you know where I really want to go? - Where?
- 巴黎 - 是的
- Is Paris. - Uh, yeah.
对 我们可以...
Yeah, you know, we can...
我们三个人可以 参加《达芬奇密码》之旅
three of us, we can do the Da Vinci Code tour.
- 对 - 是的
- Oh, yeah. - Yeah.
- 我们三个人 - 是的
- Yeah. The three of us. - Yeah.
我们三个人
The three of us.
参观那些地方...
Visit all those... those spots where...
汤姆...汤姆汉克斯...
Tom... Tom Hanks...
没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
这才是布彻尔的典型做法嘛
Now, see? That is classic Butcher.
你 离我远点
You get away from me! Get away from me!
好了 放轻松
All right, take it easy.
我不会伤害你的
I ain't gonna hurt you.
不会再伤害你了
Well, not no more.
之前也是让别人信服后就住手了
It was just enough to convince people.
你他妈的砍断了我的腿
- You chopped off my fucking leg. Yes, I did.
确实 我不会粉饰自己的行为
I ain't gonna sugarcoat it, your football days are over,
你再也踢不了足球了 不过 不用担心
but don't you worry,
我们会帮你治疗 让你恢复健康
we'll patch you up, right as rain,
你很快就会恢复工作
and you'll be back to work in no time.
工作
Work?
- 什么工作  - 还他妈的能是什么工作
- What work? - Well, what the fuck do you think?
当然是给我们造出更多的病毒啦
You're gonna make us some more of that virus.
字幕翻译:张扬
创意监督 肖雪